Gleb Stachev

Full Stack Developer

Tel Aviv | 053-897-9481 | stachev.gleb@gmail.com github.com | LinkedIn | Portfolio

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in Python and JavaScript based programming with a background in my bootcamp projects. Possess good skills in Flask and Python that help to web developing companies get good positive result from a new programmer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, OOP, Flask, Javascript.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Cards game - Github | Youtube

Find all paired cards:

- HTML template.
- CSS adaptive styling.
- JS functionality.

App Name - Github | Youtube | Render

Simple gallery with opportunity to add/delete/upgrade images and posts.

- Flask application (html (jinja2), css (bootstrap), python and js).
- Registration form, paintings uploading/upgrading form connected to PostgreSQL.
- Profile page with ability to upgrade and relation between users and posts.
- Post creation form for users (and many other small features).

EXPERIENCE

LAF LINILINGE	
Sales Manager	Vinnytsa, Ukraine
Ltd Ukrainian product	07/2014 - 03/2015
Wholesale trade in dairy products.	
Corporal	Vinnytsa, Ukraine
National Guard of Ukraine	05/2015 - 05/2016
K9 unit.	
Sales Manager	Vinnytsa, Ukraine
Ltd Tedis Ukraine	07/2016 - 04/2017
 Wholesale trade in tobacco products. 	
Unskilled jobs	Vinnytsa, Ukaraine
Eilat and Tel Aviv	07/2014 - 03/2015
 Work in a hotels (cleaner, waiter, security guard, storekeeper), work Ltd(regular worker). 	k at a factory salt of the earth

EDUCATION

Full Stock Web Dayslanment Dython and Jays Savint program	City Country
Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program	City, Country
Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp	11/2022 - 05/2023

Master's degree Vinnytsia,Ukraine

Vinnytsa Institute of Trade and Economics of State University of Trade and Economics 06/2014

LANGUAGES

Language - level (e.g. Ukrainian, Russian - native speaker, Hebrew, English - fluent)